The End
Isaac Hickentude, do you take Nigel to be your husband?
I don't. And you couldn't have told me this an hour ago.
Her name is Patience. She's a lady that lives in the ground.
What? Who was that?
We were once stuck and whole.
We decided we had to join hands and navigate our way through the dirt to the Woodstone basement.
We agreed that Sass would lead the way, then Thor, then myself.
There was another ghost in the hole with us. Her name was Patience. She was a Puritan.
What happened to her?
Isaac sneezed and let go of Patience's hand.
For all we know, she's still out there roaming.
So you're telling me there's a Puritan woman just out there wandering around in the dirt?
Yes.
Mm-mm. I don't like that one bit.
You really should have invited us to the wedding, Isaac.
He's here, Patience.
God bless you.
Oh!
Patience. The council has met and we've decided that we'd like you to leave the community.
What? But I'm the most pious among us. Who experiences less joy than I? Who is more severe?
You are joyless and severe, I agree. But even for us Puritans, there's such a thing as too severe.
I mean, you wanted us to execute Miss Elizabeth Prue.
She was talking to a doll. Tis surely a sign of witchcraft.
She's five.
And on a path most dark.
The point is you have to leave. I'm sorry.
Then fine. I shall start my own colony where there will be no smiling, no laughter, and all the handles of the butter churns shall be rough hewn so that thou shalt feel the pain of sin with every stroke.
Well, I think people are going to really enjoy that. Or not enjoy it. Whatever you wish. Anyway, banishment next.
Man, I feel bad about Isaac leaving Nigel at the altar last night. But what a show.
Indeed. At least it was a break from the crushing mundanity of our bleak existence.
Okay, the water bill this month is unusually high.
And just like that, we're back.
Jay, have you been taking long showers or something?
You think I'm taking long showers? I got a bunch of invisible people creeping on me. I wear a bathing suit in there.
People are so uptight about nudity. And the cult we used to take group showers. We really help to clean those hard to reach places.
Quick, some of them were water bill talk?
Hey guys, got those tile samples for the restaurant.
Mark and I just went to the hardware store.
Because I can leave the property?
We know, Pete.
This one's perfect. Right here. Final answer. Lock it in.
Well, okay. That was easy. It's usually a whole weird song and dance with you two.
Well, we should confirm it with our investor.
Right. Our silent partner. But do you really think he needs to weigh in on such a little thing?
Yes. I think he would be very upset if we didn't loop him in.
Yeah, that's more what I expected.
Anyway, our supplier said he's almost out of these. So if we want them, we gotta act fast.
See? So let's ask Isaac, okay? Is he in here?
No. Have any of you guys seen him?
Hmm, no. He must still be moping in this room. Oh, poor guy. But it was exciting for us.
Oh, the drama! The smell of the orders!
Where was the camaraderie? The sharing of the soul?
And she's back on group showers.
He wasn't at the hardware store because he can't leave the property, which I can.
What'd they say?
They haven't seen him. I hope he's doing okay.
Ah, I'm sure he's fine.
Okay, okay, you know what? Let's just address the elephant in the room.
You're upset with me.
Patience! Patience!
That's new.
Patience!
Hey! Sorry. Um...
Have you seen Isaac?
The marksman who only yesterday pierced my heart for a second time?
I'm sorry.
I'll be in touch, sincerentity.
I can't look back to the shed.
Oh, thank you, Giovanni Reu curb Chadwick's km of his past.
've been treated that hag-
Go ahead.
Thank you.
he would have slunk back to the shed.
Ah.
Damn it, Jay.
What? Didn't Isaac, like, totally ditch him at the altar?
Ah.
Well, we'll leave you alone.
Those of us who possess the ability to close doors will do so.
Ah.
Can you turn on the TV already?
It's not called 45 minutes.
Someone watch the full 60.
Okay, it's not just, like, pressing a button.
I mean, it is.
But it's hard, and it's impressive that I can do it at all.
Possible Trevor somehow growing weaker over time.
Legs are looking a little smaller.
What?
No.
That's not even physically possible.
Hey, have you guys seen Isaac?
I haven't seen him.
Me neither.
Not since wedding, which went very bad.
Nancy?
Have you seen Isaac?
Isaac?
Ah.
You know, now that you mention it,
I think he said he was going for a stroll this morning.
Mm-hmm.
And I remember that because when he said stroll,
I was looking at a bull, and I was like,
whoa, stroll and bull?
What are the chances?
What?
Did he say when he'd be back?
I'm sorry.
I didn't get his life story.
Jeez, what's with the third degree, huh?
Why are you being so weird?
I'm not being weird.
You're being weird.
Quit taking your body issues out on me, chicken legs.
I don't have to taste it.
No.
Interesting.
Nancy seems like she's hiding something.
Okay.
You listen here, Nancy, and you listen good.
She left, Jay.
Why am I even along on this mission?
Please, patience.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to lose you.
I-I did look for you.
A few times, I even ventured slightly into the dirt.
No, you wouldn't.
Not for patience.
Are you kidding?
I missed you.
We all missed you.
Me, Sass, Thor, the entire...
whole patrol.
I mean, we had some good times, right?
Remember when Thor tried to say the word supposedly
and instead said supposedly?
It was indeed quite amusing.
And I don't know about you, but I loved our time in the ditch.
I mean, who wouldn't enjoy staring at that gorgeous porcelain skin?
It is from the bloodletting that killed me.
I'm just glad we get to hang again.
Although, similarly to how Thor, Sass, and I miss being in the ditch with you,
I do fear I might miss being with them.
You see what I mean, patience?
Isaac is lonely.
Exactly.
I miss my friends.
You can understand that, right?
Oh, patience, understand.
Patience.
Great.
Isaac.
Nancy, out with it.
What happened to Isaac?
I don't know why you guys are riding my leg about this.
I have no idea where he is.
Okay, I had promised not to say anything, but Nancy already told me what happened.
You told him about patience?
Wait.
What happened with patience?
Oh, damn it, Stuart.
Stuart, you have to be the dumbest, most gullible piece of trash I've ever known, and I was
married to the village idiot.
Come on, Nancy.
What happened?
Okay.
So, yesterday, attracted by the pulsing bass from the wedding DJ's speakers, patience
appeared through the wall.
She asked to speak to Isaac, so we arranged a meeting.
We thought she just wanted to yell at him a little.
We didn't know she was going to drag him away.
It was very rude.
We were mad about not being invited to the wedding, but we didn't want this to happen.
Jay, a quick update.
Isaac was kidnapped by a Puritan ghost who's been roaming the dirt for centuries, waiting
for a chance at revenge.
Oh, that's really going to push back and answer on these tiles.
Obviously, I'm also very concerned for Isaac.
Thor confused how patience just take Isaac.
Not like she's strong enough to lift Isaac Dover's shoulder.
Probably be something you struggle with as well.
I broke a Thighmaster once, Thor.
I broke it.
Patience is real stealth.
I'll show you.
I'll be Patience, and, Sass, you be Isaac.
Okay?
See, he was standing over there.
Right here?
Yep, but his back was to the wall.
Like this?
Exactly.
Then all of a sudden...
Patience!
Okay, you gotta believe me.
We did not know that was gonna happen.
Surprise!
Patience!
What is the meaning of this?
Thou didst say that thou missed thy friends.
Tis now a problem solved.
Wait, did I get kidnapped because Isaac said he was lonely?
No!
I have been vastly misunderstood.
And also she has gone quite mad.
Okay?
Isaac didst inform me how much you searched for Patience all those years ago.
It was a relief on account of how much I did see thee as friends.
Uh...
Same.
Oh, I never had such friends as in the ditch!
And now we have another chance.
Huzzah.
It is ordained.
We shall spend the remainder of eternity here together.
Now, it is time for my daily constitutional.
It took me a century to get my bearings here in the dirt.
So don't you go wandering off, lest she be lost forever.
Oh, this sucks.
Yeah.
Okay, Flower, you spoke with Patience while you were in the well.
Do you recall her saying anything that could help us locate Isaac and Sass?
Don't love the Flower's memories load-bearing here.
Okay, let me think.
It's interesting because Patience has taken Isaac and now Sass.
It's almost like she's abducting everyone that was in the ditch with her.
Which just leaves Thor.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, she could be coming for you next, big guy.
The final piece to her creepy little puzzle.
I would like to see her try.
Thor not scared.
Oh, wait.
I do remember something about Patience.
She was small.
She had no arms and legs.
She was a worm.
There was a worm named Patience?
Yeah, I named her after this other Patience I met.
She's a Puritan.
And we're in the vicinity.
Do you know where we can find the Puritan?
Yes, Patience said something about living in a cave underneath a willow.
Okay, Flower said that Sass and Isaac are under a willow.
Is there a willow tree on the property?
Yeah, remember?
That's where I crashed my drone that looks like a TIE fighter.
TIE fighter's from Star Wars.
Star Wars is a futuristic space opera.
Well, actually, it was set in a distant past.
This is worse than Samantha's water bill talk.
What are we waiting for, huh?
Let's go get him.
Get who?
No!
What the hell?
Full not scared, Thor.
Just surprised.
Subtle but important difference.
Maybe being imprisoned in this dank lair with that interminable dripping is my comeuppance.
What are you talking about?
I've disappointed everyone who's ever depended on me.
I was a bad fiancé in death, a bad husband in life.
Let this be my promise to you, my friend.
If, by the grace of God, we ever get out of here, I vow to change my ways.
To be kinder, to be less selfish, to be a better person.
Good for you.
Your rock looks more comfortable.
Can I have it?
What happened to being a better person?
What?
Oh, no, no, no.
I said if.
If we get out of here.
God has to uphold his end of the bargain first.
I can't believe her in this situation.
Who knows what that lunatic has in store for us.
Oh, honestly, I'd like to say that she became terrible because of the isolation, but she
was always a little off to begin with.
Patience!
Your version's too sane.
Oh, yeah, that's it.
That was good.
That one really captured the madness.
It wasn't me, Isaac.
Patience!
What's up, girl?
I'm tired and my hands hurt.
Yeah, sorry I couldn't find that second shovel, Jay.
You throw behind the sheds, Sam.
Out going!
Thor, get over here.
All good in this open space with clear views of all approaches, but not scared.
Oh, I think he broke through.
Sam, I think I broke through.
Do you see anything?
Sus!
Isaac!
Trevor!
Arrow Guy!
Oh, this is fun naming everyone.
Oh, it's a burrow of rabbits.
No, ghost.
They're not in there.
Patience ain't in there.
You can stop cowering, Thor.
And your hat's small and ugly like Trevor's legs.
Two for one!
Boom!
Wait a minute.
Patience never said she lived under a willow.
The Grateful Dead said we could all get high under a willow in the song Sugar Magnolia,
which wasn't released until after I died, but Bobby Weir used to sing it to us in the shower.
They're not in there, Jay.
You know what that means.
We're digging in the wrong place.
Raiders.
Did Pete do the Raiders thing?
Our friends are still being held hostage, but yes, Jay, he did the Raiders thing.
My guy.
I want it to be nice.
But no one's nice to Patience.
There's only one thing to do.
Yes.
One thing to do.
Forget this ever happened and start over with a clean slate?
Take thee into the dirt.
And when you say thee, do you mean me thee or he thee?
Both.
Don't love that.
Three, two, one, shoot.
Yeah.
What was that?
You just made a fist.
That is what rock is, Stuart.
The rules are so simple, you're killing me.
The sexual tension between these two.
It's palpable.
Will they or won't they?
Just put us out of our misery.
Oh, my God.
That was gross.
Oh, that is so scary and disgusting.
I'm pretty sure a worm went right through my mouth.
Oh, she's back and she wants more.
Here, take him.
He's not annoying.
No.
I'm returning them.
Thou art free to go.
Wait.
Really?
Why?
Tis mine own fault for thinking you actually liked me.
Patience shall return to her one true friend.
The dirt.
Oh.
Oh, my god.
Why does paper beat rock?
Do I run into the dirt?
I got it.
Patience said she was living in a white room with black curtains.
No.
Wait.
That's from a bath I took with the band cream.
This is painful.
If legs hurt from standing, you would have the whole seat.
I was talking about flour.
The legs are great.
We have returned.
Oh!
How did you escape?
Did you brave the dirt?
Or did you have to do something you can never talk about?
You can tell Birdie. Birdie keeps her mouth shut.
Actually, she just let us go.
Sasapi's hurt her feelings.
Me? You did it too.
But you started it by imitating her.
Patience. Patience.
That's a thing she does now. It's nuts.
Look, I'm glad to be back, but I don't know, man.
I feel like she needed friends, and we abandoned her.
Just like we did 130 years ago.
Patience!
I'm not even exaggerating. That is literally what it is.
She is loony.
Well, I think we figured out what's up with the water bills.
Mark says the fountain is leaking.
Just hundreds of dollars dripping into the ground.
And the fascinating saga of the water bill continues.
Will they patch the pipes? Stay tuned.
Babe, Sas and Isaac escaped Patience's clutches.
They're back. Oh, nice.
You see, sometimes this ghost stuff just resolves itself.
That's a good lesson for the future.
Wait a minute. Dripping?
Isaac, remember the dripping in Patience's lair?
Patience's lair must be under the fountain.
What? She's been 50 feet away this entire time?
Oh, now that creeps me all the way out.
You know, if Patience's feelings were really hurt,
now you can do something about it. We know where she is.
Hey, just to clarify, are you suggesting going and getting
the creepy, feral Puritan ghost and bringing her into the house?
I'm suggesting righting a wrong that happened a long time ago.
Wow, and you wouldn't even let me get a lizard.
May I just remind you that this lunatic kidnapped and held us hostage?
Yeah, she was hurting, Isaac. And also she let us go.
Wait, you were kidnapped by a worm?
I may regret this, but I feel we need to go get Patience.
Patience is very creepy, but for no pain of abandonment,
would not wish that on any Nandane.
Isaac, you were literally just saying that if we got out of there,
you'd turn over a new leaf and be a better person.
Well, here's your chance.
Yes, perhaps we could start with something smaller.
I could compliment one of Samantha's dreadful sweaters.
That looks...
lovely.
Isaac.
Okay, fine, fine.
Let's go get that scary Puritan woman.
Jay, we may need to destroy the fountain, but...
Please don't finish that sentence.
No, I got a better idea. I'm a guy with great legs and a great idea.
Wow, Jay, this is actually really cool.
They formed a human chain or, you know, a ghost chain.
Once again, Sam, we're still human. We're just dead.
This is the most amazing sight I've never seen.
You see, back at Camper Ma, I was anchor of my tug-of-war team.
Three years running, we got first at the Maccabia games.
Okay.
I'll take Crash's hand.
At least we know he cannot sneeze.
Yeah, yeah, keep going. Into the dirt.
I hate this!
Ah!
Wee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee!
Whoa! Now we stop. Stop. Stop. Pull out! Pull out!
No, the ghost got pulled into the dirt.
Oh, no.
Yes! Steve Money and his magic quads!
Yeah! Suck it, Thor!
Thor's way up there.
Pass it on!
Suck it, Thor! Pass it on!
Patience! We came back!
Isaacs, Sasapis, what is the meaning of this?
We're not gonna abandon you again. Come with us!
Ah!
Oh, sorry! Sorry!
I got him! We're good. We're good. Look, we know we messed up, but you're our friend.
And you're not a lunatic.
My point is we'd like you to come back to the house with us.
You came back for me?
Not soon enough.
Patience! Patience!
Oh! So it can be good or bad. That's interesting.
Come with me if you want to live.
Terminator. It's a movie. A movie's like a series of images.
Can we do this back at the house?
Suck it, Thor! Pass it on.
Wait.
Hey, Jay. If I were kidnapped and trapped in an underground lair,
would you risk an eternity in the dirt for the chance to save me?
Ooh, of course. And I love that these are our hypotheticals.
Mm.
Well?
Oh, sorry, bro. It's a no-go on the tiles.
Our investor wants to see other options.
I mean, Burgundy.
Are we opening a restaurant or a brothel?
Okay.
I'll find some more options.
Sorry, Mark.
By the way, how's Patience adapting to life in the house?
I think it's going really well.
One last question for the...
What is thy favorite color?
Ugh, I did not sign up for this.
Patience! Patience!
Ah! Purple!
Oh.
h Apple music!
żeby去 sokной
Thank you.